junebugweddings.com 2016-04-05

# Junebug Weddings | Privacy Policy

_Last updated: October 14, 2014_

## Your Privacy Rights

Thank you for taking the time to read our Privacy Policy. Please be sure to also read our Terms and Conditions. Use of JunebugWeddings.com constitutes an agreement to these Terms and Conditions and acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

JunebugWeddings.com is owned and published by JBW Media, Inc. doing business as Junebug Weddings (collectively "Junebug Weddings").

Junebug Weddings's data collection and use policy regarding users of the site is set out in this policy. Junebug Weddings reserves the right to modify this policy as appropriate; please note the date of the most recent revision posted below the title.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

This Privacy Policy does not cover privacy provisions for sites linked to from JunebugWeddings.com.

## Definitions

The term "personally identifiable information" (PII) means any information that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or e-mail address.

The term "aggregate information" means information that does not allow us to identify or contact a specific individual but describes a general category of information about visitors to the Site, such as demographics, purchase categories (e.g., wedding dresses), or visitors using a particular browser to access the site.

The term "cookies" means small data files placed on your computer by a Web site so that the site can personalize the site and track personal site usage.

## Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

The only PII we collect from users of this site is information voluntarily submitted through our Contact Pages and Sign Up for Our Newsletter forms. This information includes names, phone numbers, wedding locations, business names, and e-mail addresses. This data may be used to contact users that have submitted information and to provide attribution for materials or information submitted and used on JunebugWeddings.com. Last names, phone numbers, and electronic mail addresses of brides and couples submitting material to our site will not be published. Junebug Weddings will offer users opportunities to participate in surveys, and options to sign up to our mailing lists to receive specific information. We will provide only that information when responding to those requests. Of course, we will comply with any legal requests for release of information. _Please note that Junebug Weddings has never sold any of our PII, but we do reserve the right to sell this information to third parties on a highly limited basis._

## Aggregate Information

We track the aggregate usage of JunebugWeddings.com. This data may include, but is not limited to, your Web browser, which Web site you visited before opening Junebug Weddings and the Web site you link to as you leave our site. We also track which pages within the site that you visit and how long you spend at each page. This information can allow us to see what pages are the most valuable and interesting to our users and enables us to provide users with a richer and more useful experience on JunebugWeddings.com.

This aggregate information does not contain any information that can be used to personally identify a specific individual.

## Cookies

The Junebug Weddings site uses cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. Junebug Weddings may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password. Junebug Weddings may use an outside ad company to display ads on the Junebug Weddings site. These ads may also contain cookies. While Junebug Weddings uses cookies in other parts of its Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by Junebug Weddings’s ad company and Junebug Weddings does not have access to this information.

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use on our sites and software. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our users to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site and/or software. Junebug Weddings and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to the Junebug Weddings properties and/or software. Our properties do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows Junebug Weddings and these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

## Global Positioning System

Global Positioning System (GPS) tracking technology may need to be enabled in Junebug Weddings products and services in order to determine the location (latitude and longitude) of users of the Junebug Weddings products and services. This information is transmitted to Junebug Weddings, Junebug Weddings’s users, and temporarily stored by Junebug Weddings. Junebug Weddings does not provide this information to any other third party. This information is used in conjunction with Junebug Weddings’s applications and Web site and enables Junebug Weddings’s users to search for local events and track other users’ locations who share common interests.

## Use of this Web Site by Minors

The privacy and protection of children is very important to us. With this in mind, we do not allow children under the age of 16 to submit information to our site. Should we become aware that someone under the age of 16 has supplied information to us, all of that information will be deleted.

## Linked Web Sites

JunebugWeddings.com contains links to the Web sites of our featured wedding professionals. If you follow one of these links to another Web site, you will leave the JunebugWeddings.com site and this Policy will no longer apply to your use of, and activities on, the other Web sites. Please read the legal notices for those other Web sites, including their privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for any Web sites linked from JunebugWeddings.com.

## Successors and Assigns

This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of successors and assigns of Junebug Weddings.

## Policy Changes

Junebug Weddings reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy in order to address future developments of JunebugWeddings.com, or industry or legal changes. If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please feel free to contact us at [Junebug Weddings](mailto:contact@junebugweddings.com).

Junebug Weddings can be reach via electronic mail: [contact@junebugweddings.com](mailto:contact@junebugweddings.com)

This mailbox does not accept solicitations.

Our address is

Junebug Weddings   
Attn: Legal   
507 W 17th St Austin, Texas 78701

Tel: 888.418.6149

Email: [contact@junebugweddings.com](mailto:contact@junebugweddings.com)
